Barbara B. Kennelly Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Legislation, 1981-1998
    - HR 5192 - Government Operations: School Boards on ACIR, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 41)
    - HR 5238 - Energy and Commerce: Orphan Drug Act, 1991 (Box 11:, Folder 42)
    - HR 5238 - Ways and Means - Orphan Drug Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 43)
    - Calendar: Drunk Driving Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 44)
    - Calendar: Hunger in the Land of Plenty, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 45)
    - H Con Res 249 - Calendar: International Policy on Religious Persecution, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 46)
    - H Con Res 260 - Calendar: Congrats on James Dozior Rescue, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 47)
    - H Con Res 275 - Calendar: Resolve MIA Problem, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 48)
    - H Con Res 278 - Calendar: Senior Citizens Community Service Employment Funding, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 49)
    - H Con Res 278 - Funding for Community Service Employment Programs, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 50)
    - H Con Res 298 - Calendar: Cost of Living Adjustment Social Security, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 51)
    - H Con Res 298 - Calendar: Old Age Survivors Disability Insurance, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 52)
    - H Con Res 302 - Calendar: Ida Nudel, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 53)
    - H Con Res 303 - Energy and Commerce Funds for EPA, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 54)
    - H Con Res 330 - Ida Nudel, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 55)
    - H Con Res 339 - Calendar: Release Tatyana Lozansky, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 56)
    - H Con Res 355 - Calendar: Geriatric Nursing, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 57)
    - H Con Res 355 - Calendar: Nursing Home Standards, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 58)
    - H Con Res 359 - Calendar: National Disabled Vets Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 59)
    - H Con Res 364 - Calendar: Jim Thorpe Olymic Medal, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 60)
    - H Con Res 378 - Calendar: Baha'i Persecution Condemned, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 61)
    - H Con Res 379 - Calendar: Civil Liberties, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 62)
    - H Con Res 381 - Calendar: Food Distribution for Hungry, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 63)
    - H Con Res 430 - Foreign Affairs: Lebanon Security Zone, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 64)
    - H Res 314 - Calendar: Imposition of Import Fee on Crude Oil, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 65)
    - H Res 344 - Calendar: 100th Anniversary of Knights of Columbus, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 66)
    - H Res 371 - Calendar: Natural Gas Price, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 67)
    - H Res 375 - Calendar: G.S. Loan Elegibility, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 68)
    - H Res 398 - Calendar: Release of Murhenko and Fiodorov, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 69)
    - H Res 409 - Calendar: Energy Policy, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 70)
    - H Res 418 - Calendar: 100th Anniversary of Knights of Columbus, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 71)
    - H Res 421 - Rules: Select Committee on Children, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 72)
    - H Res 422 - Calendar: Higher Education Funding, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 73)
    - H Res 427 - Interior: Wilderness Preservation, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 74)
    - H Res 427 - Mineral Leases in Wilderness Areas, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 75)
    - H Res 430 - Calendar: Oil Import Restrictions, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 76)
    - H Res 443 - Calendar: Convention - Prevent Genocide, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 77)
    - H Res 497 - Calendar: Opposition Increase Elderly Expenses, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 78)
    - H Res 532 - Calendar: Historic Site of Rhodes Tavern, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 79)
    - H Res 558 - Calendar: Rescind Regulations Under 94-142, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 80)
    - HJ Res 272 - Calendar: Medic Alert Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 81)
    - HJ Res 304 - Calendar: National Inventors Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 82)
    - HJ Res 386 - Calendar: Baltic Freedom Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 83)
    - HJ Res 403 - Calendar: Democratic Participation in UN, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 84)
    - HJ Res 408 - Calendar: National Cerebral Palsy Month, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 85)
    - HJ Res 412 - Calendar: National Amelia Earheart Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 86)
    - HJ Res 416 - Calendar: Child Abuse Prevention Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 87)
    - HJ Res 417 - Calendar: Lupus Awreness Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 88)
    - HJ Res 418 - Calendar: Supplemental Appropriations DHHS, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 89)
    - HJ Res 426 - Calendar: Prohibit Military Assistance for El Salvador, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 90)
    - HJ Res 428 - Calendar: National POW/MIA Recognition, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 91)
    - HJ Res 430 - Calendar: World Food Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 92)
    - HJ Res 431 - Calendar: National Theatre Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 93)
    - HJ Res 433 - Calendar: Freeze and Reduction in Nuclear Arms, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 94)
    - HJ Res 435 - Calendar: Cabanataun Prisoner of War Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 95)
    - HJ Res 447 - Calendar: National Day of Reflection, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 96)
    - HJ Res 454 - Calendar: National Cystic Fibrosis Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 97)
    - HJ Res 455 - Calendar: National Junior Bowling Championship Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 98)
    - HJ Res 456 - Calendar: National Respiratory Therapy Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 99)
    - HJ Res 459 - Calendar: American Indian Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 100)
    - HJ Res 460 - Calendar: Women's History Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 101)
    - HJ Res 474 - Calendar: Ratification of SALT II, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 102)
    - HJ Res 479 - Calendar: National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 103)
    - HJ Res 482 - Calendar: National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 104)
    - HJ Res 486 - Calendar: National School Bus Safety Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 105)
    - HJ Res 492 - Calendar: National Sewing Month, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 106)
    - HJ Res 496 - Calendar: National Alzheimer Disease Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 107)
    - HJ Res 498 - Calendar: Myasthenia Gravis Awareness Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 108)
    - HJ Res 507 - Calendar: Interpreters for Deaf, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 109)
    - HJ Res 516 - Calendar: National Coin Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 110)
    - HJ Res 518 - Calendar: National NCO / Petty Officers Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 111)
    - HJ Res 521 - Foreign Affairs: Nuclear Freeze and SALT II, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 112)
    - HJ Res 521 - Foreign Relations: Arms Control Negotiations, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 113)
    - HJ Res 524 - Calendar: National Adult Day Care Center Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 114)
    - HJ Res 526 - Calendar: National Purple Heart Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 115)
    - HJ Res 531 - Calendar: National Parkinson's Disease Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 116)
    - HJ Res 533 - Calendar: Women's Rights, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 117)
    - HJ Res 539 - Calendar: National Snowmobiling Month, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 118)
    - HJ Res 545 - Interior: Stops OCS Oil and Gas Leasing Plans, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 119)
    - HJ Res 551 - Calendar: Prohibit Child Labor Regulations, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 120)
    - HJ Res 552 - Calendar: El Salvador Certification Null and Void, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 121)
    - HJ Res 567 - Calendar: Child Nutrition, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 122)
    - HJ Res 568 - Calendar: Robert Goddard Day, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 123)
    - HJ Res 571 - Calendar: Arms Control, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 124)
    - HJ Res 588 - Calendar: Head Start Week, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 125)
    - HR 4709 - Government: Prompt Payment Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 126)
    - HR 4861 - Energy and Commerce: American Conservation Corps, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 127)
    - HR 4873 - Judiciary: Commemoration Medal to Roy Wilkens, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 128)
    - HR 5133 - Energy and Commerce: Fair Practices in Automotive Produces Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 129)
    - HR 5351 - Judiciary Charter: Daughters of the Colonists, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 130)
    - HR 5432 - Banking: Admiral Rickover Medal, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 131)
    - HR 5437 - Judiciary: Law Enforcement Officer Protection Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 132)
    - HR 5485 - Social Security: Extend the Deadline for Student Benefits, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 133)
    - HR 5485 - Ways and Means - Old Age, Survivors, and Disability Insurance, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 134)
    - HR 5507 - Social Security: Uncashed Checks to Trust Fund, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 135)
    - HR 5507 - Ways and Means - Amendment to Title II of Social Security Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 136)
    - HR 5543 - Merchant Marine: OCS Revenue Sharing, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 137)
    - HR 5553 - Interior: Miami Indians, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 138)
    - HR 5555 - Energy and Commerce: Clean Air Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 139)
    - HR 5600 - Veterans Affairs: Survivors of Sacrifice, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 140)
    - HR 5608 - Armed Services: Chemical Mutations, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 141)
    - HR 5608 - Foreign Affairs: Arms Controls, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 142)
    - HR 5653 - Energy and Commerce: Office of Smoking and Health, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 143)
    - HR 5654 - Ways and Means: Amend Omnibus, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 144)
    - HR 5705 - Judiciary: Home Recording Act of 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 145)
    - HR 5728 - Armed Services: Firefighting and Base Security Function, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 146)
    - HR 5834 - Banking: Single Family Residences, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 147)
    - HR 5853 - Post Office: Voluntary Pay Cut re RIF's, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 148)
    - HR 5893 - Ways and Means - Chemotherapy and Medicare, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 149)
    - HR 5894 - Public Works and Transportation: Vending Machines, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 150)
    - HR 6009 - Ways and Means - Enterprise Zone Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 151)
    - HR 6045 - Ways and Means - Rules on Taxing, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 152)
    - HR 6087 - Interior: Office of Water Research, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 153)
    - HR 6091 - Interior: Mary Bethune House, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 154)
    - HR 6100 - Public Works: Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 155)
    - HR 6170 - Public Works: Drunk Driving Bill, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 156)
    - HR 6239 - Ways and Means - Tariff Rates on Roses, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 157)
    - HR 6347 - Post Office: Poland Mailings, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 158)
    - HR 6386 - Judiciary: Armed Robbery and Burglary Prevention, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 159)
    - HR 6467 - Judiciary: Pro Sports Stabilization Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 160)
    - HR 6538 - Calendar: Tennyson Guyer Federal Building, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 161)
    - HR 6538 - Public Works: Federal Building in Lima, Ohio, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 162)
    - HR 6546 - House Administration: Limit Income of Senators, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 163)
    - HR 6565 - Energy and Commerce: Superfund 'owned' to 'owned and operated', 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 164)
    - HR 6576 - Education and Labor: Age Discrimination Employment Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 165)
    - HR 6576 - Ways and Means - Prohibition of Mandatory Retirement and Employment Rights Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 166)
    - HR 6591 - Public Works: Federal Capital Invesment Budget Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 167)
    - HR 6596 - Judiciary: Weapons, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 168)
    - HR 6612 - Interior: Connecticut Indian Settlement, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 169)
    - HR 6616 - Social Security: Pensions Under Public Retiement System, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 170)
    - HR 6693 - Ways and Means - Industrial Bond Reform Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 171)
    - HR 6704 - Ways and Means - Mortgage Subsidies, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 172)
    - HR 6740 - Ways and Means - Mortgage Subsidy Bonds, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 173)
    - HR 6781 - Education and Labor: Residential Mortgage Investment Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 174)
    - HR 6781 - Ways and Means - Residential Mortgage Investment Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 175)
    - HR 6916 - Ways and Means - National Nursing Home Standards Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 176)
    - HR 6932 - Judiciary: Federal Incorporation, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 177)
    - HR 6973 - Ways and Means - Old Age, Survivors, and Disability Insurance, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 178)
    - HR 6985 - Education and Labor: Vocational Education Act for Older Americans, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 179)
    - HR 7003 - Merchant Marine & Fisheries: Connecticut Salmon, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 180)
    - HR 7023 - Ways and Means - Repeal Medicare Tax on Federal Employment, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 181)
    - HR 7188 - Armed Services: Restore Social Security Vietnam Widows, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 182)
    - HR 7191 - Judiciary: Victim and Witness Protection Act, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 183)
    - HR 7337 - Banking: Emergency Shelter Demo, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 184)
    - HJ Res - Hartford 350th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 11:, Folder 185)
    - HJ Res 102 - Designation 1985 as the 350th Anniversary of the State of Connecticut (Box 11:, Folder 186)
    - HR 1770 - Health Insurance Availibility Act - Risk Pool Legislation, 1985 (Box 11:, Folder 187)
    - H Res 18 - Opposition of Import Fee on Crude Oil, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 188)
    - HR 181 - Social Security and SSI for the Homeless Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 189)
    - HR 286 - Homeless Persons Survival act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 190)
    - HR 592 - Fixing Technical problem wih ection 601(E) of Internal Revenue Code {Letter}, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 191)
    - HR 1001 - Child Care Opportunites for Families Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 192)
    - HR 1255 - Family Investment Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 193)
    - HR 1365 - Amend Title XX of Social Security Act 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 194)
    - HR 1696 - Work Opportunities and Retraining Compact of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 195)
    - HR 1720 - Family Welfare Reform Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 196)
    - HR 2183 - Rural Letter Carrier Simplification Act, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 197)
    - HR 2295 - Repeal 3 month holding requirement for regulated companies, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 198)
    - HR 2334 - Stewart B. McKinney National Wildlife Refuge Designation Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 199)
    - HR 2470 - Medicare Catastrophic Protection Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 200)
    - HR 2577 - Economic Equity Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 201)
    - HR 2613 - Pension Reform Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 202)
    - HR 2640 - Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 203)
    - HR 2712 - Appropriations for the Department of the Interior, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 204)
    - HR 2713 - Appropriations for the government of the District of Columbia, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 205)
    - HR 2714 - Appropriations for Legislative Branch, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 206)
    - HR 2977 - To Amend the Internal Revenue Code, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 207)
    - HR 3121 - To Amend the Internal Revenue Code, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 208)
    - HR 3346 - Taxpayer Safeguard and Protection Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 209)
    - HR 3375 - To Ammend the Internal Revenue Code, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 210)
    - HR 3438 - To Ammend the Internal Revenue Code, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 211)
    - HR 3454 - Medicid Home and Community Quality Services Act of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 212)
    - HR 3587 - Child Support Enforcement Amendments of 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 213)
    - H Con Res 40 - Soviet Force in Baltic States, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 1)
    - H Con Res 50 - UN Action Regarding the US Treatment of the Baltic Republics, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 2)
    - H Con Res 246 - Relation of Trade Agreements to Health, Safety, Labor, and Environmental Laws, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 3)
    - H Res 40 - Sense of Congress on Rape and Incest, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 4)
    - H Res 234 - Negotiations With Baltics for Removal of Soviet Troops, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 5)
    - H Res 297 - Renew Voluntary Restraint Arrangements with Japan and Taiwan, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 6)
    - H Res 319 - Supporting Peace Corps in Armenia and Ukraine, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 7)
    - HJ Res 23 - National Family Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 8)
    - HJ Res 91 - Pediatric AIDS Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 9)
    - HJ Res 130 - National Ellis Island Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 10)
    - HJ Res 138 - Disease Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 11)
    - HJ Res 141 - Senior Nutrition Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 12)
    - HJ Res 142 - National Campus Crime and Security Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 13)
    - HJ Res 152 - Christopher Columbus an Honorary U.S. Citizen, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 14)
    - HJ Res 154 - Foster Care Month, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 15)
    - HJ Res 167 - Baltic Freedom Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 16)
    - HJ Res 183 - National Childrens Day (BBK Sponsor), 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 17)
    - HJ Res 189 - National Firefighters Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 18)
    - HJ Res 194 - Infant Mortality Awareness Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 19)
    - HJ Res 201 - Geography Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 20)
    - HJ Res 207 - Boy Scouts of America Commemoration, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 21)
    - HJ Res 212 - National Visiting Nurse Associations Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 22)
    - HJ Res 215 - National Military Families Recognition Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 23)
    - HJ Res 219 - National Scleroderma Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 24)
    - HJ Res 230 - World Food Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 25)
    - HJ Res 261 - World Population Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 26)
    - HJ Res 267 - Parents of Twins (BBK Sponsor), 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 27)
    - HJ Res 303 - Crime Prevention Month, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 28)
    - HJ Res 327 - Designates 1992 as "Year of the Gulf of Mexico", 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 29)
    - HJ Res 340 - National Red Ribbon Week, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 30)
    - HJ Res 343 - Girl Scouts of the United States of America - 80th Anniversary Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 31)
    - HJ Res 350 - Irish-American Heritage Month, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 32)
    - HJ Res 356 - Bicentenial of the District of Columbia, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 33)
    - HJ Res 372 - Basketball Centenial Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 34)
    - HJ Res 376 - World AIDS Day, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 35)
    - HR 134 - Taxes: Terminally Ill Pre-Payment Benefits, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 36)
    - HR 392 - Family Planning and Title X, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 37)
    - HR 618 - Deduction for State and Local Sales Tax, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 38)
    - HR 689 - MFN Bulgaria and Romania 3 yrs., 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 39)
    - HR 1007 - Energy Conservation, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 40)
    - HR 1067 - Mortgage Revenue Bonds, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 41)
    - HR 1141 - Debt Pools, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 42)
    - HR 1298 - Federal Employee's Pay Comparability Act, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 43)
    - HR 1434 - Interest on Life Insurance, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 44)
    - HR 1513 - Exclude from Gross Income the Value of Transport - Van Pools, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 45)
    - HR 1566 - Amend IRS Code of 1986, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 46)
    - HR 1735 - Retirement Income Security (BBK Sponsor), 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 47)
    - HR 1876 - BBK's Suspend Duty on Ceramic Mugs, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 48)
    - HR 1877 - Duty on Non-Metal Jewelry, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 49)
    - HR 1878 - BBK's to Suspend Duty on Porcelain Ornaments, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 50)
    - HR 2174 - To Amend Title XIX of Social Security Act, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 51)
    - HR 2292 - Mammography and Medicare, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 52)
    - HR 2692 - Mammography, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 53)
    - HR 3248 - Spousal or Child Support Obligations, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 54)
    - HR 3249 - Establish a Presidential Commission on Insurance, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 55)
    - HR 3325 - Aid to Families, Dependent Children, and Small Business, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 56)
    - HR 3410 - Health Care Bill, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 57)
    - HR 3628 - FBI Education, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 58)
    - HR 3677 - Support Enforcement Improvement Act, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 59)
    - HR 3750 - Amend Federal Election Campaign Act of 1971, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 60)
    - HR 3828 - Amend IRS Code of 1986, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 61)
    - HR 3975 - Equal Remedies Act, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 62)
    - HR 3981 - Establish Goods and Services Through US Commercial Centers, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 63)
    - HR 4095 - To Increase No. of Weeks Benefits Payable Under the Emergency Unemployment Comp. Act of 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 64)
    - H Res 538 - Commending Rescuers of Jews During Holocaust, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 65)
    - H Con Res 282 - Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 66)
    - HJ Res 191 - National Law Enforcement Week, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 67)
    - HJ Res 244 - American Hispanic Literature Month, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 68)
    - HJ Res 390 - Greek Independence Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 69)
    - HJ Res 395 - National Women and Girls in Sports Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 70)
    - HJ Res 396 - National Recycing Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 71)
    - HJ Res 397 - National Correction Officer Week, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 72)
    - HJ Res 398 - National Neighborhood Crime Watch Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 73)
    - HJ Res 400 - Italian-American Heritage Month, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 74)
    - HJ Res 409 - National Good Teen Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 75)
    - HJ Res 410 - Education and Sharing Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 76)
    - HJ Res 427 - Irish Brigade Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 77)
    - HJ Res 433 - National Domestic Violence Awareess Month, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 78)
    - HJ Res 435 - Commemorative Postage Stamp in honor of Louis 'Satchmo' Armstrong, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 79)
    - HJ Res 457 - Religious Freedomn Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 80)
    - HJ Res 459 - Lyme Disease Awareness Day, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 81)
    - HJ Res 495 - National Women Veterans Recognition Week, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 82)
    - HJ Res 500 - Irish-American Heritage Month, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 83)
    - HR 3410 - Balenced Budget Act, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 84)
    - HR 4175 - Infrastructure Projects in Distressed Areas, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 85)
    - HR 4300 - Stewart B. McKinney Homeless Assistance Act, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 86)
    - HR 4312 - Voting Rights Improvement Act, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 87)
    - HR 4343 - Amend Solid Waste Disposal Act, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 88)
    - HR 4405 - Repeal the Provision Which Includes Unemployment Compensation in Income Subject to Tax, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 89)
    - HR 4416 - Dire Emergency Job Creation Appropriations Act, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 90)
    - HR 4539 - Larkin R. Smith Mississippi Post Office, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 91)
    - HR 4727 - Extend Emergency Unemployment Compensation Program, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 92)
    - HR 4750 - Stabilize Emissions fo Carbon Dioxide to Protect Global Climate, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 93)
    - HR 4756 - Amend the Omnibus Trade and Competitiveness Act of 1988, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 94)
    - HR 4821 - To Amend the IRS Code to Allow Credit For First Time Home Buy, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 95)
    - HR 4925 - Suspension of Duty on Wicker Products, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 96)
    - HR 4926 - Suspend Duty on Certain Glass Articles, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 97)
    - HR 4927 - Economic Conversion, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 98)
    - HR 5026 - Bill to Amend Communications Act of 1934, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 99)
    - HR 5333 - Balanced Budget, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 100)
    - HR 5423 - Quinebaug and Shetucket River Valley National Heritage Corridor, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 101)
    - HR 5440 - Amend IRS Code of 1986, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 102)
    - HR 5495 - Public Health Service Act, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 103)
    - HR 5600 - Family Preservation Child Welfare, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 104)
    - HR 5651 - Provide for Retirement to Ex-Spouses of Employees of CIA, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 105)
    - HR 5731 - Interstate Taxation Commission, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 106)
    - HR 5820 - Emergency Unemployment Compensation, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 107)
    - HR 5957 - Antipersonnel Landmines, 1992 (Box 12:, Folder 108)
    - HR 224 - Civil Rights - Equal Remedies Act of 1993 (Box 12:, Folder 109)
    - HR 841 - Defense Economic Reinvestment Act of 1993 (Box 12:, Folder 110)
    - HR 1193 - National Voluntary Service and Educational Oppurtunity Act of 1993 (Box 12:, Folder 111)